# **Hoang Quoc Tran**

**PROFILE** 

I'm a CTU graduate specializing in Human computer interaction and someone who has always been passionate about visually pleasing aesthetics. As a designer, I aim to create interfaces with usability and users' needs in mind. As a developer I create interactive experience using technologies such as React, Typescript.

**EXPERIENCE** 

# Frontend developer | Centrum Znalostního Managementu

July 2018 - July 2022

- Took part in the development of multiple platforms aimed at students and employees of CTU Faculty of Electrical Engineering.
- Worked with variety of different languages, frameworks such as JavaScript, TypeScript, jQuery, React etc.
- Communication with project managers, designers and other stakeholders on a daily basis.

# UX designer | Centrum Znalostního Managementu

January 2019 - July 2020

- Redesigned multiple already integrated applications used at CTU FEE
- Designed parts of new platforms aimed at students of CTU FEE
- Practical use of UCD process

#### Lead UX designer | Centrum Znalostního Managementu

July 2020 - July 2022

- · Lead an UX team consisting of 3 junior members
- · Created a light design system to be used in future designs
- Conducted several complex user researches
- Usability testing as a part of design process
- · Created wireframes, prototypes for a number of applications

#### **EDUCATION**

### Bachelor degree - Computer Software Engineering

CTU Faculty of Electrical Engineering

October 2016 - June 2019, Prague

## Master's degree - Open Informatics

CTU Faculty of Electrical Engineering

October 2019 - February 2022, Prague

hoang.t.q@seznam.cz +420 721 198 728 linkedin.com/hoangtq

#### **SKILLS**

# **Programming Languages**

JavaScript (ES6), TypeScript,
HTML, CSS, Python, Java

#### Libraries and Frameworks

 jQuery, React, NextJs,
TypeScript, styledcomponents, zustand

# Design

Figma, Adobe XD

#### **PROJECTS**

#### Hub

An application whose main goal was to integrate dozens of already used faculty applications into one unified system for a more comprehensive user experience.

#### VisualClass

A prototype of an interactive videoconferencing tool to be used as a part of distance education.

#### LANGUAGES

- · Czech (native)
- · Vietnamese (native)
- English (C2 proficiency)

#### **INTERESTS**

- Football
- Bouldering
- Chess